All right. You're done. Let's take a look at my solution. All right. So, here's
what our addLocation function looks like, locationSetting, cityName,
latitude and longitude. Just like in our content
provider test, we can use getContentResolver to query
based upon the content URI. Remember that the
default location entry CONTENT_URI passes all of the
parameters into the database. So we can easily
construct a query containing the location setting to see if
it's in the database yet. If it's not, then the query
will return an empty set and we should insert the new
city name, location setting, latitude, and longitude into the database together.